https://toggler.com/privacy-policy

TOGGLER® Plastic Toggle Anchors
Hang paintings, prints, mirrors, etc. quickly, easily and securelySpecially-designed, built-in hook holds the weight of the application on the screw, not below itProvides maximum holding and prevents pull-out
Carry twice the load than standard wing anchorsSmallest installation hole for each bolt sizeProvide superior holding with metal-to-metal fastening
Holds securely in walls & ceilingsUnique locking action resists vibration and shockStrongest holding of all self-drilling drywall anchors
Strongest in solid materialsHolds securely even in hollow walls or ceilingsPolypropylene body seals hole
Use in almost any material5/16” drill hole required for installation159 lb max hold in 5/8” drywall
Expansion Anchors
Ankr-TITE® Wedge Anchor
Original Wej-It® Wedge Anchor
Sleeve-TITE™ Sleeve Anchor
Threaded Anchors
POWER-Skru™ Large Diameter Concrete Screw
Wej-Con® Concrete Screw
Hang-TITE™ Rod Hanger Screw
Ankr-TITE® Wedge Anchor
Provides precise, rapid expansionEnlarged 3 dimple clipLength identification code stamped on each anchor
Original Wej-It® Wedge Anchor
Use for light to normal weight concrete and solid masonryGuiding notch on the anchor headMinimize wedge loosening under vibratory load
Sleeve-TITE™ Sleeve Anchor
From lightweight concrete and hollow masonry to normal weight concrete and solid masonry applications
Strike-It™ Center Pin Drive Anchor
Easy to installDepth of hole not criticalYellow dichromate finish is corrosion resistant
Screw-In™ Drive Screw Anchor
Easy to installFor use in concrete, block, brick or stonePre-assembled, ready to use
Drive-It™ Drive Pin Anchor
Easy to installIdeal for light-duty and tamper-resistant applicationsCorrosion resistant zamac alloy body
Slam-It™ Split Drive Anchor
Easy to installFor use in concrete and stoneTamper-proof
Pound-It™ Drive Anchor
Easy to installPre-formed one-piece designFor use in concrete, grout-filled block, or masonry
POWER-Skru™ Large Diameter Concrete Screw
Heat treatment provides surface and core hardnessSerrated head facilitates a positive lockCan be removed and reinstalled
Wej-Con® Concrete Screw
Cuts threads in structural materialSurface coating for corrosion resistanceDrill bit included in each box
Hang-TITE™ Rod Hanger Screw
For steel purlins, lightweight to normal weight concrete, wood & timber, hollow core and concrete plank applications
Ultra-Drop™ Drop-In Anchor
Easy to installOffers consistent holding power in shallow embedmentEliminates requirement for rod couplings
Hollo Set™ Drop-In Anchor
Easy to installOffers consistent holding powerAllows easy removability for service work
POWER-Drop™ Drop-In Anchor
Internally threaded anchorWedge performance with the convenience of drop-inNumerous head style options
Single Expansion Shield
Holding power unaffected if bolt is removed and replacedEntire fastener is corrosion-resistantAllows easy removability for service work
Double Expansion Shield
Expands fully to provide high gripping powerEliminates high stress pointsAllows easy removability for service work
Lag Screw Shield
Ideal for concrete, masonry and mortar jointsZamac alloy finish is corrosion resistantAllows easy removability for service work
Machine Screw Shield
For use with a machine bolt in concrete, block, brick or stoneFits into irregular holesSetting tool provided in each box of anchors
Standard Toggle Bolt
Easy snap-open actionFor use in wallboard/drywallSpreads load over a wide area
Self-Drilling Drywall Anchor
For wallboard and drywall 3/8” – 1”
SDS-plus® with Hex Shank Drill Bit
Centering tip reduces bit walkingReduced friction during dust removalDecreased vibration back into the tool
Wej-Con® Concrete Screw Drill Bit
Carbide-tipped drill bit for Wej-Con ScrewsReduced vibration and noiseReduced breakage when encountering rebar
Spline Drill Bit
Centering tip reduces bit walkingReduced friction during dust removalDecreased vibration back into the tool
SDS-plus® Premium Drill Bit
Centering tip reduces bit walkingReduced friction during dust removalDecreased vibration back into the tool
SDS-Max® Drill Bit
Carbide-tipped drill bit with 6 cutting edgesReduced vibration and noiseReduced breakage when encountering rebar
POWER-Sert™ Adhesive Insert Anchor
Machine lathed from a single pieceExclusive FRICTION-FIT™ allows immediate fasteningEasy installation
Inject-TITE™ (AW) All-Weather
Bonds to smooth diamond core drilled holesFor both solid and hollow base materialsStyrene-free
Inject-TITE™ (FS) Fast-Set
Won’t shrink or sagFor both solid and hollow base materialsSolvent-free, allowing for greater flexibility
Adhesive Dispensing Tools
High-quality adhesive dispensing tools provide reliable and accurate functionality on the job siteColor of dispensing tool subject to change
Epoxy Screen Tubes
Epoxy screen tubes help shape and form epoxy in hollow materials.
Epoxy Mixing Nozzles
Epoxy mixing nozzles unique design evenly mixes the 2-part epoxy
L-Bolt Anchors
Single-piece and easy to install in wet concreteMade with high-grade steelNuts and washers are included
Browse all products
Ask the Experts
Where to Buy
About
View Catalog
Browse all products
Home
Contact
FAQ
Home
privacy-policy
Privacy Policy
TOGGLER Privacy PolicyThis Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit toggler.com (the “Site”). Personal information we collect As with many websites, when you visit the Site, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the Site, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the Site, and information about how you interact with the Site. We refer to this automatically-collected information as “Device Information”. We collect Device Information using the following technologies: - “Cookies” are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org. - “Log files” track actions occurring on the Site, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps. - “Web beacons”, “tags”, and “pixels” are electronic files used to record information about how you browse the Site. How do we use your personal information? We use the Device Information that we collect to help us screen for potential risk and fraud (in particular, your IP address), and more generally to improve and optimize our Site (for example, by generating analytics about how our customers browse and interact with the Site, and to assess the success of our marketing and advertising campaigns). Sharing your personal Information We also use Google Analytics to help us understand how our site visitors use the Site—you can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here: https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/. You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout. Finally, we may also share your Device Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights. Do not track Please note that we do not alter our Site’s data collection and use practices when we see a Do Not Track signal from your browser. Your rights If you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that any personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below. Please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to Canada and the United States. Changes We may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons. Minors The Site is not intended for individuals under the age of majority—normally 18 or 21 years of age depending on the jurisdiction. Contact us For more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact us by email at sales@toggler.com or by mail using the details provided below:TOGGLER High-Performance Anchors[Re: Privacy Compliance Officer] 110 Richards Ave, #1Norwalk CT 06854 USAWej-it Privacy PolicyThis Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit wejit.com (the “Site”). Personal information we collect As with many websites, when you visit the Site, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the Site, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the Site, and information about how you interact with the Site. We refer to this automatically-collected information as “Device Information”. We collect Device Information using the following technologies: - “Cookies” are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org. - “Log files” track actions occurring on the Site, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps. - “Web beacons”, “tags”, and “pixels” are electronic files used to record information about how you browse the Site. How do we use your personal information? We use the Device Information that we collect to help us screen for potential risk and fraud (in particular, your IP address), and more generally to improve and optimize our Site (for example, by generating analytics about how our customers browse and interact with the Site, and to assess the success of our marketing and advertising campaigns). Sharing your personal Information We also use Google Analytics to help us understand how our site visitors use the Site—you can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here: https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/. You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout. Finally, we may also share your Device Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights. Do not track Please note that we do not alter our Site’s data collection and use practices when we see a Do Not Track signal from your browser. Your rights If you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that any personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below. Please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to Canada and the United States. Changes We may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons. Minors The Site is not intended for individuals under the age of majority—normally 18 or 21 years of age depending on the jurisdiction. Contact us For more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact us by email at sales@wej-it.com or by mail using the details provided below:Wej-It High-Performance Anchors[Re: Privacy Compliance Officer] 110 Richards Ave, #1Norwalk CT 06854 USA
